VIP STUDENTS I
WANT TO EXPLAIN
EXACTLY WHAT THE
DM AND THIS
PAGE THAT YOU'RE
ON RIGHT NOW
IS ABOUT FIRST
OFF IF YOU
SAW THE PRICE
CHANGE, DON'T WORRY
YOUR CURRENT PRICE
IS LOCKED IN
LIKE NO MATTER
WHAT IF YOU
JOIN A MEMBERSHIP
WE'RE NOT GONNA
INCREASE THE PRICE
OF YOUR MEMBERSHIP
TIER SO LIKE
YOUR GRANDFATHERED IN
BUT THE REASON
I'M MAKING THIS
PAGE IS ABOUT
MY COACHING LOOK
SOMEWHERE NEAR TO
THE END OF
THIS YEAR SOMEWHERE
IN THE NEXT
COUPLE MONTHS HAVEN'T
CONFIRMED THE DATE.
WE'RE GONNA BE
REMOVING ME OKAY
FROM THE VIP
EXPERIENCE FROM ONE
-ON -ONE COACHING
AND THE REASON
FOR THAT IS
WE'RE GROWING REALLY
REALLY FAST AND
WE ALMOST ARE
SOLD OUT ALREADY
AND BY THE
END OF THE
YEAR. I'M SURE
WE'LL HAVE HUNDREDS
OF VIP STUDENTS
SO IT'S JUST
IT'S NOT POSSIBLE
FOR ME CONTINUING
TO DO LIKE
ALL THE ONE
-ON -ONE COACHING
BUT SINCE WE
ARE INCREASING THE
PRICE RIGHT NOW,
I WANTED TO
GIVE YOU GUYS
THE OPTION IF
YOU WANT TO
LOCK IN YOUR
CURRENT RATE EVERYTHING
YOU SIGNED UP
FOR THE FOUNDERS
PRICE ALL THAT
AND MAINTAIN COACHING
ACCESS TO ME
SO THIS PAGE
WAS BASICALLY LIKE
FOR PEOPLE WHO
PREPAY IF YOU
WANT THE OPTION
TO IF YOU
PREPAY SIX MONTHS
OR YOU SIGN
UP FOR A
YEAR YOU CAN
LOCK IN NOT
JUST YOUR CURRENT
PRICE, BUT ALSO
ACCESS TO ME
AND THE REASON
I'M DOING THIS
IS BECAUSE SELFISHLY
IT'S GOOD FOR
ME TO HAVE
SOME COACHING FOR
YOUTUBE CONTENT AND
CLIPS AND ALL
THIS STUFF AND
YOU KNOW ALL
THE YOUTUBE SHORTS
AND YOU SEE
BUT IT'S NOT
GOOD FOR ME
TO HAVE A
HUNDRED STUDENTS AND
SO I WAS
THINKING OF LIKE
HOW CAN I
YOU KNOW GIVE
LIKE A CRAZY
GOOD DEAL AND
STILL YOU KNOW
KEEP A FEW
OF MY COACHING
STUDENTS AND THAT'S
WHY I WANTED
TO MAKE THIS
FOR YOU GUYS
SO OBVIOUSLY, YOU
KNOW LIKE IF
YOU KNOW MY
HOURLY RATE, YOU
KNOW MY HOURLY
COACHING IS USUALLY
LIKE I THINK
IT'S LIKE A
HUNDRED EIGHTY A
LITTLE UNDER 200
BUCKS RIGHT NOW
SO IT'S SAFE
TO SAY THAT
THIS DEAL THAT
YOU'RE GETTING IS
LIKE IT'S REALLY
GOOD DEAL BUT
TO KIND OF
REWARD YOU GUYS
FOR BEING FOUNDERS
MEMBERS I WANTED
TO GO TO
YOU FIRST AND
GIVE YOU GUYS
THIS OPTION OBVIOUSLY,
NO PRESSURE LIKE
WE'RE GONNA RESERVE
YOUR PRICE EITHER
WAY BUT IF
YOU WANT DM
ACCESS TO ME
THROUGH THE NEXT
SIX MONTHS OR
THE NEXT 12
MONTHS REST OF
THE YEAR WHATEVER
YOU SIGN UP
FOR I JUST
WANTED TO GIVE
YOU THAT OPTION
TO LOCK IT
IN AND EITHER
WAY LIKE YOU
KNOW YOUR CURRENT
PRICE WILL STAY
THE SAME BUT
THAT'S WHAT THIS
PAGE IS ABOUT
SO IF YOU'RE
INTERESTED IN THAT
ACCESS TO ME
PLUS I THREW
IN A LITTLE
BONUS LOWER IN
THE PAGE THAT
I HAVEN'T DONE
IN OVER FIVE
YEARS IF YOU'RE
INTERESTED IN THAT
JUST READ THE
PAGE ALL THE
DETAILS ARE BELOW
AND IF YOU
DO UPGRADE TO
DM BACK I
LOOK FORWARD TO
CONTINUING TO WORK
WITH YOU. THAT'S
MY PIECE. THANKS
GUYS