QUICK ONE. EVERYONE
WHO HASN'T SEEN
JUST DROPPED AN
ANNOUNCEMENT. THE PRICE
OF THE VIP
EXPERIENCE IS GOING
UP NEXT SUNDAY.
FOR THOSE YOU
DIDN'T SEE, THE
VIPS NEARLY SOLD
OUT. WE'RE AT
ALMOST 50 OUT
OF 60 MEMBERS.
AND SO NEXT
SUNDAY, NOT THIS
ONE, THE PRICE
IS GOING TO
BE INCREASING. AND
DON'T WORRY, LIKE
IF YOU'RE CURRENTLY
A VIP, YOUR
GRANDFATHER, DAN, AT
THE PRICE YOU'RE
AT, LIKE WE'RE
NOT, YOU KNOW,
CHANGING THE PRICE
FOR ANYBODY WHO'S
THE CURRENT MEMBER,
BUT IT'S GOING
UP FOR NEW
STUDENTS. AND I
WANTED TO GIVE
YOU GUYS THE
OPPORTUNITY BEFORE THAT
PRICE CHANGE AND
BEFORE WE SELL
OUT, OBVIOUSLY TO
GET IN FOR
THE NEXT SEVEN
DAYS IF YOU'RE
INTERESTED AT THE
CURRENT PRICE. REGARDLESS,
IF YOU'RE CURRENTLY
ON VIP, YOUR
PRICE IS GOING
TO STAY THE
SAME. YOU'RE LOCKED
IN AS LONG
AS YOU CONTINUE
TO STAY ACTIVE
AND CONTINUOUS WITH
YOUR MEMBERSHIP. BUT
I JUST WANT
TO MAKE THIS
QUICK LIKE ANNOUNCEMENT
IN CASE YOU
ALL, YOU KNOW,
DIDN'T SEE TO
HAVE ON THE
PAGE. IF YOU
WANT MORE DETAILS,
WE'LL EXPLAIN, YOU
KNOW, WHY THE
PRICE IS GOING
UP AND WHEN
EXACTLY IT'S GOING
UP BELOW AND
ALL THE REASONS
FOR IT. THERE'S
SOME DETAILS IN
THERE ABOUT MY
COACHING, WHY WE'RE
DOING THIS, WHAT
THIS CHANGES FOR
THE FUTURE. IT'S
REALLY EXCITING THAT
WE ARE SOLD
OUT, THAT WE
HAVE SO MANY
PEOPLE ON THIS
VIP, BUT OBVIOUSLY
TO DO IT,
IT TAKES NOT
JUST MY TIME,
BUT THE COACH'S
TIME. SO EVERY
VIP STUDENT ISN'T
JUST LIKE, YOU
KNOW, SHINY ROLL
IN THE SERVER,
BUT IT'S ACTUALLY
A LOT OF
TIME THAT WE
POUR INTO. AND
SO I APPRECIATE
YOU GUYS, LIKE,
BLOWING UP THE
VIP EXPERIENCE. IT'S
SO COOL THAT
IT'S DOING WELL.
SO MANY OF
YOU ARE OBVIOUSLY
BENEFITING FROM IT.
AND I JUST
WANT TO MAKE
THIS POST TO
BASICALLY GIVE YOU
NOTICE, RIGHT, TO
JUST BE TRANSPARENT
ABOUT WHAT WE'RE
CHANGING AND WHY
WE'RE CHANGING IT.
AND I MADE
THIS LITTLE WEB
PAGE FOR YOU
TOO, WITH CLAUDE
CODE TO HOPEFULLY
EXPLAIN ALL OF
IT. SO YEAH,
IF YOU HAVE
ANY QUESTIONS, READ
BELOW. I JUST
WANTED TO EXPLAIN
THIS, YOU KNOW,
QUICK VIDEO, SHOOT
THIS QUICK VIDEO
SO THAT ALL
OF YOU SAW
AND JUST HAD
VISIBILITY ON THAT.
APPRECIATE YOU GUYS.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL
SEE YOU BACK
WHEN I'M BACK
IN CHICAGO, MY
NEXT EVENT. AND
THANKS FREAKY FOR
SOMETHING FOR MY
MONTHLY COACHING. PEACE,
GUYS.